Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files
1951-1990
1977-1986
Vassar College. Office of the President
Smith, Virginia B.
73 cubic feet (73 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials related to the work of the Vassar College's Office of the President during the tenure of Virginia B. Smith. The collection includes typical day-to-day administrative records, as well as documents related to noteworthy issues and events from the Smith Era (1977-1986).
Biographical Note
Virginia B. Smith was the eighth President of Vassar College. Before coming to the college, she had built a formidable reputation as an economist, attorney, and leader in higher education. She was born in Seattle, Washington, attended the University of Washington as well Columbia University, and worked for a variety of organizations and institutions, including the University of California, Berkeley; the Carnegie Commission on Higher Education; and the U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare's Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education (FIPSE).
Scope and Content Note
Materials related to the work of the Vassar College's Office of the President during the tenure of Virginia B. Smith. The collection includes typical day-to-day administrative records, as well as documents related to noteworthy issues and events from the Smith Era (1977-1986). Topics include divestiture from South Africa, student protest over an invitation to William F. Buckley, Jr. to speak at Commencement, the expansion of the manuscript collections in the Library's Archives and Special Collections, and one of the largest capital campaigns in Vassar's history.
Access
Some files in this collection are restricted and labeled as such in the container list. Other material may need to be vetted before being released. The rest is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Additional material may be found in the Archives and Special Collections Library in:
The VC Biographical Files
The VC Photograph Files
Virginia B. Smith Personal Papers
Subject Headings
Names:
Buckley, William F., Jr., 1925-2008
Organizations:
Vassar College--Presidents; Vassar College--Administration; Vassar College--Public relations; Vassar College--Students; Vassar College--Library
Subjects:
Women--Education; African Americans--Study and teaching; Blacks--Study and teaching; College students--Political activity; Investments, American--South Africa
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Presidents
Encoding Information
Encoded by Zachary Bodnar and Laura Streett, December 2014. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, March 2024.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Vassar College Office of the President, 2002. Additional materials transferred in 2004 (A2004-006), 2005 (A2005-008), 2009 (A2009-012), and 2011 (A2011-002).
Series List
- Series I. Trustees, 1976-1980; (Boxes 1-3)
- Series II. Faculty, 1967-1986; (Boxes 4-7)
- Series III. Alumnae/i, 1950-1987; (Boxes 7-11)
- Series IV. Within the College, 1971-1988; (Boxes 12-20)
- Series V. Associations, 1976-1987; (Boxes 20-25)
- Series VI. Schools and Colleges, 1964-1982; (Boxes 25-26)
- Series VII. Special Projects, 1982-1984; (Box 26)
- Series VIII. General Correspondence, 1977-1980; (Box 27)
- Series IX. Additions, 1951-1997; (Boxes 27-73)
Container List
- Series I. Trustees
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Villard, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.1)
  - Trustees — General, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.2)
  - Trustees — J, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.3)
  - Board of Trustees — Agenda, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.4)
  - President’s Reports to Trustees, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.5)
  - Reports to Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1978 (Folder 1.6)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.7)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1977 (Folder 1.8)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec 1977 (Folder 1.9)
  - Report of Proceedings, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1978 Mar 1 (Folder 1.11)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1978 (Folder 1.12)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1978 Mar 29 (Folder 1.13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1978 Jun 6 (Folder 1.14)
  - Audit Committee, 1978 (Folder 1.15)
  - Budget Committee, 1977-1976 (Folder 1.16)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1978 (Folder 1.17)
  - cIcu Committee of Correspondence, 1977 (Folder 1.18)
  - Development Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.19)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.20)
  - VC-AAVC Development Coordinating Council, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.21)
  - Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.22)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.23)
  - Governance Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.24)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.25)
  - Investor Responsibilities Committee (Trustees’), 1978 (Folder 1.26)
  - Minority Students Committee, 1978 (Folder 1.27)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1977-1978 (Folder 1.28)
  - Student Representation on the Board (Extra Copies of Report), 1977 (Folder 1.29)
  - Faculty and Studies Meeting, Mar 9, 1977 (Folder 1.30)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 1.31)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee Meeting, Mar 9. 1977 (Folder 1.32)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee Meeting, Jun 7, 1977 (Folder 1.33)
  - Extra Copies — Minutes (Board and Executive), 1977-1978 (Folder 1.34)
  - Extra Copies — Reports to Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1978 (Folder 1.35)
  - Extra Copies — Reports to Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb 1978 (Folder 1.36)
  - Extra Copies — Reports to Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec 1977 (Folder 2.1)
  - Extra Copies — Reports to Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1977 (Folder 2.2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Nov 29, 1977 (Folder 2.3)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting, Feb 1978 (Folder 2.4)
  - Agenda and Schedule of Committee Meetings, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.5)
  - Trustees — B, 1977-1979 (Folder 2.6)
  - Trustees — C, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.7)
  - Trustees — D, 1977-1979 (Folder 2.8)
  - Trustees — E, 1977-1979 (Folder 2.9)
  - Trustees — F, 1977 (Folder 2.10)
  - Trustees — H, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.11)
  - Trustees — M, 1979 (Folder 2.12)
  - Trustees — O, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.13)
  - Trustees — R, 1977-1978 (Folder 2.14)
  - Trustees — S, 1977-1979 (Folder 2.15)
  - Trustees — T, 1977 (Folder 2.16)
  - Trustees — W, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.17)
  - Audit Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.18)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes, 1977-1979 (Folder 2.19)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting — Resolutions Adopted at Meeting, Oct 1978 (Folder 2.20)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting, Oct 1978 (Folder 2.21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec 1978 (Folder 2.22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb 1979 (Folder 2.23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1979 (Folder 2.24)
  - President’s Reports to Trustees, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.25)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees Executive Session, May 19, 1979 (Folder 2.26)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 19, 1979 (Folder 2.27)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Students’ Building, May 19, 1979 (Folder 2.28)
  - Report of Proceedings, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.29)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Mar 27, 1979 (Folder 2.30)
  - Governance Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.31)
  - Nominations Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.32)
  - I.R.C — South Africa Study Group Joint Meeting, Aug 14 (Folder 2.33)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 2.34)
  - J. and W. Seligman Reports to Trustee — Investments and Finance Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 3.1)
  - Minority Students Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 3.2)
  - Personnel Committee — Board of Trustees, 1980 (Folder 3.3)
  - Student Life Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 3.4)
  - Resolution in re Mandatory Retirement Age, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.5)
  - Trustees — Emeriti, 1976-1977 (Folder 3.6)
  - Trustees — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.7)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.8)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Villard, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.10)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.11)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Sep 21, 1978 (Folder 3.12)
  - Personnel Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.13)
  - Investor Responsibility Committee (Trustees’), 1978-1979 (Folder 3.14)
  - Committee on Investor Responsibility, 1979 (Folder 3.15)
  - Trustee IRC — Pending, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.16)
  - Minority Students Committee, 1979 (Folder 3.17)
  - Equestrian Program, 1976-1979 (Folder 3.18)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Athletics, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.19)
  - Trustees Study on the Board of Trustees, 1978 (Folder 3.20)
  - Report of Proceedings (Extra Copies), 1978-1979 (Folder 3.21)
  - Extra Copies — Minutes of Board Meetings, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.22)
  - Ad hoc Committee on Priorities (Folder #1), 1979 (Folder 3.23)
  - Ad hoc Priorities Committee Meeting, 1979 (Folder 3.24)
  - Ad hoc Committee on Priorities (Folder #2), 1979 (Folder 3.25)
  - Budget Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.26)
  - Committee on Buildings and Grounds, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.27)
  - cIcu Committee of Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.28)
  - Development Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.29)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.30)
  - Extra Copies — Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.31)
  - VC-AAVC Development Coordinating Council, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.32)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 3.33)
- Series II. Faculty
  - Departmental Budget Requests (Book I), 1978-1979 (Folder 4.1)
  - Departmental Budget Requests (Book II), 1978-1979 (Folder 4.2)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1977-1978 (Folder 4.3)
  - Faculty — General, 1976-1978 (Folder 4.4)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, Jan 1, 1978 – Jun 30, 1978 (Folder 4.5)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, Jul 1, 1977 – Dec 31, 1977 (Folder 4.6)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1979-1980 (Folder 5.1)
  - Agendas — Faculty Meetings, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.2)
  - Appeal Committee, 1979 (Folder 5.3)
  - Ad Hoc Committees, 1978 (Folder 5.4)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.5)
  - Faculty — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.6)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.7)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.8)
  - Faculty Committees, 1976-1979 (Folder 5.9)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.10)
  - Committee on Committees, 1979 (Folder 5.11)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, Jan 1, 1979 – Jun 30, 1979 (Folder 5.12)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, Nov 1978 – Jan 1, 1979 (Folder 5.13)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, Jul 1, 1978 – Nov 1978 (Folder 5.14)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 5.15)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.16)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1976-1978 (Folder 5.17)
  - Faculty and Student Budget Review, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.18)
  - Committee on Faculty Procedure, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.19)
  - Committee on Fellowships, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.20)
  - Investor Responsibility Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.21)
  - Secretary of the Faculty, 1977 (Folder 5.22)
  - Committee on Lectures, 1976-1977 (Folder 5.23)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.24)
  - Faculty Policy and Conference Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 5.25)
  - Faculty on Policy and Conference, 1976-1978 (Folder 5.26)
  - Poynter Fellowship Committee, 1974-1978 (Folder 5.27)
  - College Regulations Committee, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.28)
  - Committee on Research, 1977-1979 (Folder 5.29)
  - Overview Committee — Report on Size, Composition and Diversity, Jan 29, 1980 (Folder 5.30)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1981 (Folder 5.31)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies Meeting, 1980-1981 (Folder 5.32)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies Meeting, 1979-1980 (Folder 5.33)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies Meeting, 1979 (Folder 5.34)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Priorities, 1979 (Folder 6.1)
  - Faculty Publications, 1979-1980 (Folder 6.2)
  - Salary and Compensation Study — Department of Economics, Dec 1, 1979 (Folder 6.3)
  - Faculty Salary and Appointments Committee (FASC), 1979-1983 (Folder 6.4)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee (FCC), 1981 (Folder 6.5)
  - Dean Sullivan (FASC) — Extension of First-Term Assistant Professor, 1982 (Folder 6.6)
  - FASC, 1982 (Folder 6.7)
  - Campus Budget Review Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 6.8)
  - Faculty Committees, 1986 (Folder 6.9)
  - Committee on Committees, 1984-1986 (Folder 6.10)
  - Communications Committee, 1982-1984 (Folder 6.11)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies Meeting, 1982-1984 (Folder 6.12)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1981-1982 (Folder 6.13)
  - Curricular Changes, 1981 (Folder 6.14)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1983-1985 (Folder 6.15)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1983-1985 (Folder 6.16)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies Meeting, 1981-1983 (Folder 6.17)
  - FCC Meeting, 1979-1981 (Folder 6.18)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 6.19)
  - Faculty Policy and Conference Committee, 1978 (Folder 6.20)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1979-1981 (Folder 6.21)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1979-1980 (Folder 6.22)
  - Faculty Research Committee, 1983-1985 (Folder 6.23)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, 1977-1981 (Folder 6.24)
  - Special Faculty Meeting — VBS, 1985-1986 (Folder 6.25)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Apr 10, 1985 (Folder 6.26)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Nov 13, 1985 (Folder 6.27)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Dec 11, 1985 (Folder 6.28)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Jan 23, 1985 (Folder 6.29)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Mar 6, 1985 (Folder 6.30)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Feb 6, 1985 (Folder 6.31)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Nov 14, 1984 (Folder 6.32)
  - November Faculty Meeting Minutes (Delivered by Bob DeMaria), Nov 14, 1984 (Folder 6.33)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Dec 12, 1984 (Folder 6.34)
  - Faculty Meeting, May 9, 1984 (Folder 6.35)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1984-1985 (Folder 6.36)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Sep 12, 1984 (Folder 6.37)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1983-1984 (Folder 6.38)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1984 (Folder 6.39)
  - Faculty Publications and Professional Activities, 1980-1983 (Folder 6.40)
  - President Smith’s Remarks at Faculty Meeting, Feb 8, 1984 (Folder 6.41)
  - President Smith’s Remarks at Faculty Meeting, Sep 14, 1983 (Folder 6.42)
  - Faculty Meeting, May 7, 1986 (Folder 7.1)
  - Faculty Policy and Conference Committee, 1978-1980 (Folder 7.2)
  - President Smith’s Remarks at Faculty Meeting, Sep 14, 1983 (Folder 7.3)
  - Meeting of the Faculty, May 4, 1983 (Folder 7.4)
  - President Smith’s Remarks to Faculty Meeting, Apr 13, 1983 (Folder 7.5)
  - Faculty Meeting, Apr 13, 1983 (Folder 7.6)
  - Faculty Meeting, Feb 16, 1983 (Folder 7.7)
  - Faculty Meetings — VBS, 1982-1983 (Folder 7.8)
  - Faculty Meeting, Mar 23, 1983 (Folder 7.9)
  - Faculty Meeting, Dec 8, 1982 (Folder 7.10)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1981-1983 (Folder 7.11)
  - President Smith’s Remarks at Faculty Meeting, Oct 6, 1982 (Folder 7.12)
  - Faculty Meeting, Nov 10, 1982 (Folder 7.13)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, May 5, 1982 (Folder 7.14)
  - Faculty Meeting, Apr 14, 1982 (Folder 7.15)
  - Special Faculty Meeting — VBS, Jan 20, 1982 (Folder 7.16)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Dec 9, 1981 (Folder 7.17)
  - Faculty Meeting, Nov 11, 1981 (Folder 7.18)
  - Faculty Meeting, Oct 14, 1981 (Folder 7.19)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Sep 9, 1981 (Folder 7.20)
  - Special Faculty Meeting, May 13, 1981 (Folder 7.21)
  - Special Faculty Meeting, May 7, 1981 (Folder 7.22)
  - Faculty Meeting, May 6, 1981 (Folder 7.23)
  - Faculty Meeting, Apr 22, 1981 (Folder 7.24)
  - Special Faculty Meeting, Apr 4, 1981 (Folder 7.25)
  - Faculty Meeting, Mar 25, 1981 (Folder 7.26)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Feb 11, 1981 (Folder 7.27)
  - Faculty Meeting, Dec 10, 1980 (Folder 7.28)
  - Faculty Meeting, Nov 12, 1980 (Folder 7.29)
  - Faculty Meeting — VBS, Oct 29, 1980 (Folder 7.30)
  - Faculty Meeting, Sep 10, 1980 (Folder 7.31)
  - Special Faculty Meeting, May 12, 1980 (Folder 7.32)
  - Faculty Meeting, May 7, 1980 (Folder 7.33)
  - Faculty Meeting, Apr 9, 1980 (Folder 7.34)
  - Faculty Minutes, Sep 13, 1978 (Folder 7.35)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1982 (Folder 7.36)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1982 (Folder 7.37)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas, 1980-1981 (Folder 7.38)
  - Faculty Meeting, Jan 30, 1980 (Folder 7.39)
  - Faculty Meeting, Feb 15, 1978 (Folder 7.40)
  - VBS — Loose Faculty Meeting Documents, 1979-1984 (Folder 7.41)
  - Faculty Meetings — General, 1967-1983 (Folder 7.42)
  - Professor Tedolinda Barolini — Candidate for Antolini Chair, Feb 8, 1982 (Folder 7.43)
- Series III. Alumnae/i
  - Class Letters — AAVC, Nov 1981 (Folder 7.44)
  - Mrs. Richard Adloff — California, 1970-1978 (Folder 7.45)
  - Alumnae-i — A, 1976-1984 (Folder 7.46)
  - Alumnae — Mrs. Dante Antolini, 1972-1980 (Folder 7.47)
  - Mrs. Julian Armstrong, 1971-1973 (Folder 7.48)
  - Mrs. Tobin Armstrong — Texas and Washington D.C., 1971-1976 (Folder 7.49)
  - Mrs. Henry R. Atkinson, 1975-1979 (Folder 7.50)
  - B — General Alumnae, 1979-1987 (Folder 7.51)
  - Anne Bassage ’35, 1983 (Folder 7.52)
  - Alumnae-i — B, 1976-1978 (Folder 7.53)
  - Elizabeth Ball and Mrs. Alexander Bracken, 1973-1979 (Folder 7.54)
  - Bedell, Susanna E. ’40, 1979 (Folder 8.1)
  - Mrs. John W. Becker, 1973-1976 (Folder 8.2)
  - Mrs. Carleton Blunt ’27, 1958-1977 (Folder 8.3)
  - Mrs. Edward E. Brownell ‘00, 1969-1981 (Folder 8.4)
  - Mrs. Sidney Brody ’37, 1960-1974 (Folder 8.5)
  - Alumnae-i — C, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.6)
  - Mrs. Randolph Compton ‘17, 1969-1977 (Folder 8.7)
  - Rita Conroy ’78, 1981 (Folder 8.8)
  - Helen Cook, 1973-1979 (Folder 8.9)
  - Miss Jean E. Crego, 1973-1979 (Folder 8.10)
  - Alumnae-i — D, 1976-1985 (Folder 8.11)
  - Eleanor Daniels Drawings, 1984 (Folder 8.12)
  - Davidson-Oestreich “Program”, May 1975 (Folder 8.13)
  - Mrs. Frederick Deknatel, 1976-1982 (Folder 8.14)
  - Mrs. Walter B. Driscoll ’23, 1969-1986 (Folder 8.15)
  - Mrs. William N. Driscoll ’40, 1969-1980 (Folder 8.16)
  - Alumnae-i — E, 1976-1987 (Folder 8.17)
  - Alumnae-i — F, 1976-1984 (Folder 8.18)
  - Alumnae — Mrs. Waldron Faulkner, 1973-1983 (Folder 8.19)
  - Mrs. Robert L. Foote, 1974-1983 (Folder 8.20)
  - Mrs. Waldemar Fries and “Audubon Interlude”, 1969-1975 (Folder 8.21)
  - Alumnae-i — G, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.22)
  - Mrs. Benjamin Grey ’24, 1967-1976 (Folder 8.23)
  - Alumnae-i — H, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.24)
  - Mrs. Clarence J Hand ’07, 1972-1983 (Folder 8.25)
  - Mrs. Wellington Henderson ’25, 1969-1976 (Folder 8.26)
  - Mrs. Hess — Lunch, N.Y., 1982 (Folder 8.27)
  - Mrs. Dunham Higgins ’12, 1970-1971 (Folder 8.28)
  - Mrs. Alexander Hixon ’40, 1970-1973 (Folder 8.29)
  - Mrs. Donald F. Hyde ’34, 1950-1977 (Folder 8.30)
  - Alumnae-i — I, 1976-1979 (Folder 8.31)
  - Alumnae-i — J, 1977-1983 (Folder 8.32)
  - Alumnae-i — K, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.33)
  - Alumnae-i — L, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.34)
  - Lenfestey, Josephine E. ’34, 1980-1986 (Folder 8.35)
  - Mrs. John Loeb ’28, 1970-1982 (Folder 8.36)
  - Claudia Lyon, 1972-1977 (Folder 8.37)
  - Alumnae-i — Mc, 1976-1985 (Folder 8.38)
  - Alumnae-i — M, 1976-1986 (Folder 8.39)
  - Melly, Alice, Oct 3, 1984 (Folder 8.40)
  - Lydia Kahn Malbin ’21 (Mrs Barnett), 1970-1977 (Folder 8.41)
  - Alumnae — M — Ruth Crawford Mitchell, 1972-1984 (Folder 8.42)
  - Helen Maguire Muller (Mrs. Andre E.), 1974-1981 (Folder 8.43)
  - Alumnae-i — N, 1977-1981 (Folder 8.44)
  - Alumnae-i — O, 1978-1980 (Folder 9.1)
  - Mrs. Willis H. Sterg O’Dell, 1969-1978 (Folder 9.2)
  - Louise Olmstead — Anonymous Bequest — Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Folder 9.3)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Robert Olmstead and Nancy Olmstead, 1974-1979 (Folder 9.4)
  - Alumnae-i — P, 1976-1986 (Folder 9.5)
  - Miss Dorothy M. Parker, 1973-1977 (Folder 9.6)
  - Mrs. Duane L. Peterson, 1970-1978 (Folder 9.7)
  - Mrs. Malcolm Pitt, 1973-1979 (Folder 9.8)
  - Alumnae-i — Q, 1976-1979 (Folder 9.9)
  - Alumnae-i — R, 1976-1984 (Folder 9.10)
  - Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd ’31, 1970-1984 (Folder 9.11)
  - Mrs. Robert Rowan ’53, 1970-1984 (Folder 9.12)
  - Alumnae-i — S, 1976-1987 (Folder 9.13)
  - Mary and Leonard Schlosser, 1971-1976 (Folder 9.14)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Charles P. Schwartz ’20, 1970-1973 (Folder 9.15)
  - Mrs. C. Grove Smith (Scottie Fitzgerald ’42), 1975-1976 (Folder 9.16)
  - Mrs. S. Emlen Stokes, 1972-1980 (Folder 9.17)
  - Alumnae-i — T, 1976-1981 (Folder 9.18)
  - Alumnae-i — U, 1979 (Folder 9.19)
  - Alumnae-i — V, 1976-1984 (Folder 9.20)
  - AAUW Centennial Celebration, May 9, 1981 (Folder 9.21)
  - Alumnae-i — W, 1976-1987 (Folder 9.22)
  - Joan Watters (Mrs. Wellington), 1972-1975 (Folder 9.23)
  - Miss Florence Wilson, 1972-1979 (Folder 9.24)
  - Alumnae-i — X-Y-Z, 1976-1985 (Folder 9.25)
  - Vassar Club Visits, 1983-1984 (Folder 9.26)
  - Vassar Club Visits, 1982-1983 (Folder 9.27)
  - President’s Visits to Vassar Clubs, 1981-1982 (Folder 9.28)
  - Vassar Club Visits — Miscellaneous, 1975-1987 (Folder 9.29)
  - V.C. Visits to Houston, New Orleans and Dallas, 1980-1981 (Folder 9.30)
  - Atlanta Vassar Club, 1978-1980 (Folder 9.31)
  - Black Alumnae/i Forum II, Apr 1987 (Folder 9.32)
  - Boston Vassar Club, 1973-1978 (Folder 9.33)
  - Buffalo Vassar Club, 1979 (Folder 9.34)
  - Central Florida Vassar Club Visit — VBS, Feb 1984 (Folder 9.35)
  - Chicago Vassar Club Visit, Mar 1987 (Folder 9.36)
  - Chicago Vassar Club, 1972-1982 (Folder 9.37)
  - Chicago Opening of all Seasons and Every Light Exhibition, Nov 1984 (Folder 9.38)
  - Cincinnati V.C. Visit — DMS, 1982 (Folder 10.1)
  - Cleveland Vassar Club, 1978-1979 (Folder 10.2)
  - Dallas, Mar 1981 (Folder 10.3)
  - Delaware Vassar Club, 1978-1980 (Folder 10.4)
  - Detroit/Birmingham Vassar Club Visit, 1981 (Folder 10.5)
  - Fairfield County Vassar Club, 1977-1980 (Folder 10.6)
  - Hartford Vassar Club, 1974-1979 (Folder 10.7)
  - Hawaii, 1984; (3 folders) (Folder 10.8)
  - Houston, 1980-1981 (Folder 10.9)
  - Jersey Hills Vassar Club Visit, Sep 1981 (Folder 10.10)
  - Kansas City Vassar Club Visit, Dec 1982 (Folder 10.11)
  - London Vassar Club, 1978-1987 (Folder 10.12)
  - Maryland Vassar Club, 1976-1980 (Folder 10.13)
  - Minneapolis Vassar Club, 1977-1978 (Folder 10.14)
  - New Orleans, Mar 1981 (Folder 10.15)
  - NYC Vassar Club Visit, Apr 1987 (Folder 10.16)
  - Vassar Club of New York Dinner and Musicale The Lotus Club, Nov 20, 1986 (Folder 10.17)
  - N.Y. Vassar Club Scholarship Benefit, Apr 6, 1983 (Folder 10.18)
  - Philadelphia Vassar Club, 1975-1987 (Folder 10.19)
  - Northwestern Connecticut V.C. Visit, Sep 1981 (Folder 10.20)
  - Peninsula Vassar Club and East Bay, 1977-1980 (Folder 10.21)
  - Pittsburgh Vassar Club, 1972-1979 (Folder 10.22)
  - Poughkeepsie Area Vassar Club — Bruch at President’s House, Jan 22, 1984 (Folder 10.23)
  - Syracuse Vassar Club Trip, Apr 1985 (Folder 10.24)
  - Washington, D.C. Vassar Club Visit, May 1984 (Folder 10.25)
  - Washington Vassar Club, 1974-1987 (Folder 10.26)
  - Washington State Vassar Club, 1979-1981 (Folder 10.27)
  - Westchester Vassar Club, 1969-1979 (Folder 10.28)
  - Wisconsin Vassar Club Visit, 1981 (Folder 10.29)
  - VBS — Trip to San Diego Vassar Club, 1982 (Folder 10.30)
  - San Diego V.C. Visit, Nov 1982 (Folder 10.31)
  - San Francisco Vassar Club Visit, Nov 1984 (Folder 10.32)
  - AAVC’s Spring ’85 Tour to San Francisco, Apr-May 1985 (Folder 10.33)
  - Santa Barbara, 1979 (Folder 10.34)
  - Savannah Seminar, Mar 1978 (Folder 10.35)
  - Southern California Vassar Club, 1980 (Folder 10.36)
  - St. Louis Vassar Club, 1970-1978 (Folder 10.37)
  - New York Vassar Club, 1972-1981 (Folder 10.38)
  - Poughkeepsie Club Members (Folder 10.39)
  - Poughkeepsie Vassar Club, 1980-1981 (Folder 10.40)